<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Web Development on What, Why, How</title><link>https://jiyongcheng.dev/categories/web-development/</link><description>Recent content in Web Development on What, Why, How</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 15:23:47 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jiyongcheng.dev/categories/web-development/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to create a custom user provider in Laravel 9</title><link>https://jiyongcheng.dev/post/2023/how-to-create-a-custom-user-provider-in-laravel-9/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Apr 2023 15:23:47 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://jiyongcheng.dev/post/2023/how-to-create-a-custom-user-provider-in-laravel-9/</guid><description>Laravel provides several built-in user providers for authentication, including Eloquent and Database providers. However, sometimes you may want to use a custom data source or storage for user authentication. In such cases, you can create a custom user provider in Laravel.
For my case, our client has already had hash algorithm and function to work, I&amp;rsquo;m thinking how to use Laravel 9 to do same thing.
So in this tutorial, we will walk you through the steps of creating a custom user provider in Laravel.</description></item><item><title>Xdebug</title><link>https://jiyongcheng.dev/post/2023/xdebug/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 16:20:47 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://jiyongcheng.dev/post/2023/xdebug/</guid><description>I spent a bit of time to understand how Xdebug3.1.6 work in PHP8.1, the following is the UML sequence diagram for my understanding of Xdebug. Some notes In a Docker container, you need to tell Xdebug where to make the debugging connection to, as it is Xdebug that initiates the communication to the IDE, and not the other way around.
If we set xdebug.start_with_request=yes in 99-xdebug.ini, every request will trigger a debugging session.</description></item><item><title>Render Code Block in Bootstrap 5</title><link>https://jiyongcheng.dev/post/render-code-block-in-bootstrap5/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2021 10:39:47 +1000</pubDate><guid>https://jiyongcheng.dev/post/render-code-block-in-bootstrap5/</guid><description>&lt;h2 id="issue-found">Issue found:&lt;/h2>
&lt;p>I found the post which has code block cannot render correctly in the small devices which width is less than 576px.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>